so what are your simple acts of kindness that like warm your heart you know what i mean because
ever so often humans really do just be like you know what let me just be nice like one of mine
is uh the random god bless you when you sneeze you know i'm saying like when i'm somewhere and
i sneeze and i just hear like a bless you come from the ether it's like bless you i mean it
takes on a new meaning now because they're also just like hope you don't have covid like that's
embedded beneath that bless you and they're also like don't give it to me but i appreciate the
sentiment i also love the not walking through a picture like when you see somebody taking a
picture and they pause and when someone sees you taking a picture and they pause and let you take
the picture because it's just like you know what i see you you're probably doing something for the
instagrams or you know just because you want to remember this moment and i'm not gonna disrupt
your moment like look at you being self-aware unlike white women in target parking lots y'all be trying
to get hit for real so the other one for me is california is really good at stopping when the
ambulance is coming like all the cars will be like skirt skirt and it's like you know what
everyone has said to themselves i'm not going to be the reason that this person that they either
taking or going to pick up dies and that's nice you know that's nice it's these simple acts of
kindness that can make you feel like damn maybe maybe the world isn't comprised of genocidal maniacs
drop your simple acts of kindness that warm your little heart below
you